<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
  <ModInfo>
    <Name value="The NoMad, unforgiving lands."/>
    <Description value="         An overhaul that will make the game more challenging in several ways while helping you avoid having to back track (no need to revisit old places) and incentivates you to keep exploring the world.                  Tweaks to many mods and vanilla.         I would prefer to split this mod into many small mods to users could cherry pick just what they want, but I dont have that extra energy to do that right now.         The idea of this mod is to keep moving, scavenging everywhere, instead of building a permanent fortress.                  Tips/Suggestions(*1):         Hazards:           - radiation is a big threat now, before invading a building take rad resist chem and wear some hazmat suit parts, and try to defeat all radiative zombies inside it as soon as possible! Tho, with a full hazmat suit you can patiently climb to the top and slowly clean them while going down.           - how to quickly clean hazardous miasma: find a high spot to place water from bucket (like a not too high ceiling, 2 or 3 blocks high). Digging the floor 2 blocks deep may not provide the underwater detection required to init the bathing mode.         Progress:           - invest points in electrocutioner as it have many benefits to defense, tools and travel.           - invest points in living off the land to be able to craft more antibiotics.           - invest 1 point in: cooking, for healing with boiled meat         Hirable NPCs:           - try to get 1 or 2 molotovs to be able to kill a horde and save your first npc, beware tho that some survivors are not hirable, the hint is their names, hirable have '(NPC)' on it, and be sure it is not a raider before approaching!           - hirables' ammo and armor wont last forever, so be sure to re-hire them and repair their armor. re-hire a npc is important to refill their ammo, it is like you are paying to fill their ammo.           - position hired npcs carefully, they can help a lot if you understand how they behave         ETC.:           - you cant buy items from traders now. you can spawn them just to sell to them. the idea is that they become just a currency exchanger to deal with NPCs that can follow you, like if you were selling to NPCs directly.           - it is highly recommended to use the 1blockCrouch patch, that will give you a coherent advantage over most enemies, but unfortunately the camera will look thru blocks so dont glitch (dont shoot thru blocks). The camera positioning seems to be automatic (try to crouch below a big water pipe, it's round edges will place the camera in the correct position, I wonder if someone could dll fix that?)                  Problems/bugs and Workarounds:         - if the NPC following you start moving far away like +1KM, ride a bike, wait a few seconds to be sure they are close, and leave it, the NPC will spawn near you again.         - HazardousWeatherMod: if coretemperature stops working try on console: weathersurvival off; weathersurvival on; weather snowfall 1; weather rain 1; # then run around a bit to see if something changes. Toggle them on off 1 0, randomly til it works.. And never again use the st (settime) day or night command that seems to be what breaks weathersurvival? instead use: ggs TimeOfDayIncPerSec; take note of that value then: sgs TimeOfDayIncPerSec 1000; wait a bit and set it back to previous value.         - RadiatedParticlesOnMesh on rabbits will cause an error on log, still no idea how to prevent that, but will happen only once per spawn.                  GUNS:         - repair guns with it's parts         - dismantle guns into it's parts                  NPC DROPPED LOOT (DROP BAGS):         - changed colors based on visibility: low/medium/high quality as red/blue/yellow         - raiders always drop bags now, so lower the config to item drop/found ammount to minimum (25%)         - loot.xml constant IDs may require to be changed by you if it conflicts with someone else's mod (I may bash script that, but it will only run thru cygwin)                  NPCs (from XNPCCore and sub mods):         - good chance to drop 'their' guns, parts and ammo now.         - only one hired NPC can follow you now         - you can upgrade any NPC armor to power armor (needs re-upgrading after re-hiring to keep the price coherent), but their model wont change (that is the idea anyway, to keep the looks so you can chose the NPC you prefer to follow you)         - their armor will break out of repair after some time, so you will need to hire another NPC. Having to change the NPC will demand you to think before you finally need to do it.         - lowered HP to prevent them tanking (therefore lowered hire price)         - they have ammo limit now, after that they stop following you. you can dismiss and re-hire them. There is a warning hint when ammo is almost depleted. There is no craftable item to refill ammo because their hire price plus the powerarmor price will make it almost equivalent to just re-hiring a powerarmor npc. Also you will have to think before you need to re-hire, and their auto-dismiss will create some extra challenge.                  NV Battery and Elctrn Mods:         - IMPORTANT! If the Elctrn mods wont work just after you load the game just unequip and re-equip the armor piece it is on. There is one line on the HUD showing all active modes.         - increase max battery charge limit by improving electrocutioner perk         - craft battery charges using car battery, much better on workbench tho         - the more damaged HelmetLight, WeaponLight, NightVision and all Elctrn mods are, the worse they will work, but they can be repaired (it is a global player cvar, and not an item specific feature)                  ConfigSuggestions:         SG:         - BloodMoonFrequency 5 (good if you want it to be previsible)         - BloodMoonRange 0         SGS:         - AirDropFrequency 168 (7 days)         - AirDropMarker false         - BlooMoonDay ( to a multiple of 5, or current day if you just exit and reload the game as it may unset the bloodmoon mode right?)                  Issues:         - do not install Elctrn mods in an equipped armor, unequip, install, re-equip. If it still doesnt work, just unequip all and re-equip. The display will show what mods are active 1 and inactive 0.         - after fixing a Elctrn mod, if it was damaged exactly 10% (so would go to 0%), it may take some time to update the fixed displayed value, so just wait some time.         - NPCs (following you) extra info like armor damage, ammo spent/limit etc, are only visible on the console (F1) every 10s, as I found no way to let them be shown nearby their name/health/arrow on the HUD.       "/>
    <Author value="Ghussak"/>
    <Version value="v1.0aRC1 (A20)"/>
    <Website value=""/>
  </ModInfo>
</xml>
