<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
  <Name value="GSKlethalHS"/>
	<DisplayName value="Ghussak - Head Shots are Lethal" />
	<Description value="
		HeadShotsAreLethal reworked mod (this plays better combined with Effective and Immersive Weapons Overhaul)
		This was rethought to consider helmets' strengths, preventing instant lethality for them.
		The damage now may have a small delay to happen.
		
		TODO(somePartsMayBeDoneAlready): This is WIP. increase the abrangency of bullets and melee weapons that do more or less damage based on the visible 3D model helmet (or cranium thickness like on bears). Piercing power: BulletBall - Pistol=0, SMG=0, M60=1(7.62mm mass), Riffle=2(7.62mm mass + long barrel); AP - Pistol=3, SMG=5, M60=7, Riffle=9. BoneKnife=1, spikedClub=2(spikes are short), huntingKnife=3, machete=6 (despite shown as slash, can also pierce), steelSledgeHammer=10(No Piercing But Just Smash It All, Equivalent Final Result); Helmets: none=0(clothHelmet, hats), weak=2 (bikerHelmet, workerHelmet, plastic, direworlf, lion, fireFighterHelmet, footBallHelmet, miningHelmet), medium=4(bear, scrapIronHelmet), high=6(ironHelmet), strong=9 (army, kevlar, steelBomberZomb, mechs, steelHelmet), but this is actually just for zombies based on their 3D model, as we cant equip visible helmets on them (right?). One shot kill is only if power >= defense. W/o the armor piercing buff, normal/vanilla damage will be applied. add 25% chance to the shot miss a critical spot causing only minor damage?
		
		ISSUE?: may not work properly with raiders. Most raiders only seem to detect headshots while in full ragdoll mode (when they are starting to stand up they are not in ragdoll mode anymore). Could it be a 3d model issue? Anyway, the only way is to headshot them while in full ragdoll mode. But... that is actually a good challenge, you can only easily finish them if they get knocked down and you only have about 2s to do it!
	"/>
	<Author value="Ghussak"/>
	<Website value=""/>
	<Version value="A22v1.0_1.0"/>
	<SkipWithAntiCheat value="true" />
</xml>
